Fireworks for Elspeth is a romance, tv movie film directed by Alvin Rakoff.
Will they starve her?
Shave her head?
Force her to wear a hair shirt?
Elspeth's friends and family react with horror, grief and
even derision to her desire to become a nun.
She experiences her parents' hurt, her fiancee's feeling of betrayal,
her friends' incomprehension - and her own obstinate joy.
Elspeth, played by Fiona Shaw.
Mrs. Erskine, played by Barbara Leigh-Hunt.
Larry, played by Robert Addie.
Colin, played by Simon Cowell-Parker.
Young Elspeth, played by Katy Durham-Matthews.
Robert, played by Richard Garnett.
JoAnne Dorothy Good (born 15 January 1955) is a British radio presenter,
television presenter, broadcast journalist and actress.
The tone is emotional.